this is my introduction .My name is Aleeza Mujahid. I'm 19 years old and currently a first-year BCIT (Bachelor of Computer and Information Technology) student in Computer Science at NED University. I come from a family of five, with three siblings: an older sister and a younger brother. I'm excited to be diving into the field of computer science, where I'm eager to learn and develop skills in programming, data analysis, and software development. 

